Hello everyone, welcome
back to English Pod.
My name is Marco and
I'm Erica and today we're
bringing you again
our romantic dramatic
suspense series. I'm
sorry I love you part seven.
So we're gonna find out
what's happening with
Steven and Veronica.
Right in the last episode
Veronica was at the
doctors she was pregnant
but then the doctor
told her it was a lie and
he made it up and she
wasn't even pregnant.
Exactly so now let's see
what Veronica and Steven
are going to say to each
other maybe they will break
up. I don't know I don't
think so but let's listen.
Thank God you showed
up when you did.
He's insane. Do you think
we should call the police?
I don't worry about it. I'll call my
friend and have him take care of it.
I can't believe he was
stuck in you all these years.
What a nut job. I know.
Well he said I'm not pregnant.
I'm sorry if I got you all
worked up over nothing.
I want you to know that I didn't do it on
purpose. I don't apologize. From the moment
I met you not a day is gone
by when I haven't thought
of you and now that I'm
with you again I'm just
I'm just scared Veronica.
The closer I get to you
the worse it gets. The
thought of not being with you.
I mean I just can't
handle it. We were made
for each other Veronica.
You're my everything.
My soul mate. What
can I do? Just hold me.
I'll always be here for you no
matter what and together we can
tackle whatever
life throws at us.
I believe in us Steven.
I'm so happy to hear that.
I know we belong
together. I love you so much.
Oh my god. I don't
know. This is like so big.
I can't believe this is
happening. Well it's a very
intense drama but we saw
some great words and a lot
of great phrases in there
when Steven was telling
her all these
beautiful words right.
That's right so why don't we
look at some of these words now
in language takeaway.
Language takeaway.
Veronica was glad or was she was
very happy that Steven showed up.
That's right showed up.
So to show up. Right to come
to a place. Okay or to arrive.
That's right. So let's
listen to some examples
of how we can use show
up in different contexts.
Example one. We were waiting for you
like an hour and you never showed up.
Example two. I didn't
invite him to the party.
He just simply
showed up and invited.
Example three. After months of being lost
my dog finally showed up with a family.
All right so I think it's
pretty clear now the
verb show up and I
think this verb is a little
bit informal isn't it?
Yes you wouldn't really
tell your boss hey I'm
waiting for you to show up.
Yeah it's a it's a
bit too informal.
As you know the doctor he
was he was stalking Veronica.
That's right so that's our next word. Stock
to stock somebody. S T A L K. Okay stock.
Now this isn't a good thing
right? No this is this is bad.
So what happens when
you stock someone?
You follow them secretly
for a long time and then
maybe you you watch
them and yeah like you have
you're standing outside
their window watching them
get on dress or something.
Okay so many famous
people have stalkers right?
Yeah which is the noun.
The noun for me except so if I am stalking
somebody I am considered to be a stalker.
Yes so two stocks so don't
do this. So Stephen described
this stalker as a nut
job. A nut job. A nut job.
Okay very very informal
and it doesn't really mean
anything literally
but it's crazy.
Yes it means a crazy person.
A crazy person. What a nut job.
He's a nut job. Okay so
would you really call this
to someone like to their
face? No no definitely not.
It's definitely impolite.
Right you can't say
to someone oh you're a nut
job. Yeah but it's not a swear word.
No but it's a little
bit insulting right?
That's saying you're
crazy. Yeah but stronger.
Well the doctor was a
nut job he was stalking
her and she apologized to
Stephen for getting him worked up.
Worked up. So work up to be worked up.
When you get worked up what happens?
You get really emotional
and usually angry or sad or
upset but a negative emotion.
Okay so you got worked up.
So it's always used
with the verb to get.
So to get worked up.
Okay you get worked up.
You got worked up. Okay
very good. And well Stephen
got worked up over
nothing but he didn't mind.
He said she is his love and
he called her his soulmate.
His soulmate. Somate.
That's right a very
romantic word meaning
the perfect person for you.
Right your other half.
Yes okay so your soulmate
is that perfect compliment for
you and it's usually romantic right?
Usually romantic but sometimes you might
use it with your very very best friend.
Okay because you
understand each other.
Yeah you know what
the other one's thinking.
You're the perfect fit together.
Okay soulmate. Very good.
Well we've seen some really
interesting words so why
don't we listen to our
dialogue again and then
we'll come back and look at
some of the phrases that were used.
Thank God you showed
up when you did.
He's insane. Do you think
we should call the police?
I don't worry about it.
I'll call my friend and have
him take care of it. I
can't believe he was talking
you all these years.
What a nut job. I know.
Well he said I'm not
pregnant. I'm sorry if I got you
all worked up over
nothing. I want you to know
that I didn't do it on
purpose. Don't apologize.
From the moment I met you
not a day has gone by when
I haven't thought of
you. And now that I'm with
you again I'm just I'm
just scared Veronica.
The closer I get to
you the worse it gets.
The thought of not being with
you. I mean I just can't handle it.
We were made for
each other Veronica.
You're my everything. My
soulmate. What can I do?
Just hold me. I'll always be
here for you no matter what.
And together we can tackle
whatever life throws at us.
I believe in us Steven.
I'm so happy to hear that.
I know we belong together.
I love you so much.
That was a little bit
more clear this time but
now I want to look at
some phrases in the dialogue
and see how they can be put together.
Putting it together.
So Veronica apologized to Steven for
getting him worked up over nothing.
Over nothing. Over nothing.
Now it's the complete
sentence. I'm sorry for getting you
worked up over nothing.
So over nothing means for
no reason right exactly
so why don't we listen to
some other examples of
how we can use over nothing.
Example one. You always
get angry over nothing.
You have such a bad temper. Example two.
I called the police last night over nethin.
I thought I had a thief in my house.
Example three.
Let's not fight having nothing.
Let's just have dinner in peace.
Okay so we see you can
use many different verbs
together with over nothing.
So get excited over nothing.
Get angry over nothing.
Get upset over nothing. Exactly.
Very good so over nothing.
And now for our next phrase. So when Steven
was telling Veronica how much he loved her,
he told her not a day has gone
by when I haven't thought of you.
So not a day has gone by.
So that part of the sentence not a day
has gone by. What does he mean by that?
He means basically
every day I think of you.
There hasn't been a moment
that I haven't thought of you.
Now how can we change a little bit?
What can we change within this phrase?
Well you can put
in different times.
Okay so not a day has gone
by. Not an hour has gone by.
Not a moment has gone
by. Not a month, not a year.
Exactly. Okay so you
can use different times in
that phrase but an
important thing is that the
complement is always
negative right? That's right.
So it's always
followed by a negative.
Not a day has gone by that I
haven't wished you are here.
Okay so it's followed
by a negative.
That's right. Maybe one
more. Not a second has gone by
that I haven't missed you.
Okay very good examples.
Very romantic. Oh
Marco. All right and now
our last phrase. He told
her I'll always be here for you.
No matter what. No matter what.
No matter what. No matter
what. What does he mean by that?
Well regardless of
or you know nothing's
going to stop me. Okay
so if I want to get that job
I'm going to get
it no matter what.
So nothing's going to stop you.
Now we can change the WH word
of what at the end right?
Yes. With other ones.
Exactly so no matter
where. No matter where
you are I will find you.
Yeah no matter when.
No matter when your
birthday is I will be there.
That's right. You can see how you
can use different WH words here.
Okay very good and it's a
very common phrase right.
No matter what. No matter where.
No matter where. No
matter why. No matter how.
Yeah no matter how. Okay
so those were some really
great phrases and I think
you can play with them
a little bit change some things and then
you can use them in your everyday life.
That's right but why
don't we hear them again
one more time in
context with the dialogue.
Thank God you showed
up when you did.
He's insane. Do you think
we should call the police?
I don't worry about
it. I'll call my friend and
have him take care of
it. I can't believe he was
stalking you all these
years. What a nut job.
I know. Well he said I'm
not pregnant. I'm sorry if I
got you all worked
up over nothing.
I want you to know that
I didn't do it on purpose.
I don't apologize. From the
moment I met you not a day
is gone by when I haven't
thought of you and now
that I'm with you again I'm
just I'm just scared Veronica.
The closer I get to
you the worse it gets.
The thought of not being
with you. I mean I just
can't handle it. We
were made for each other
Veronica. You're my
everything. My soulmate.
What can I do? Just hold
me. I'll always be here for
you no matter what. And
together we can tackle
whatever life throws at
us. I believe in us Steven.
I'm so happy to hear that. I know we
belong together. I love you so much.
Okay Erica so who
do you think got shot?
I don't know but I'm
starting to think this story is
becoming a soap opera.
Well it certainly is and
well what do you guys
think happen or who do you
think got shot or
who did the shooting?
Who shot who? Maybe. Wasn't even
a gunshot. Maybe it was just the car.
The tire could have
popped. I don't know.
So we'll come to our
website tell us what you
think happens or what
you would like to happen
because I know many
people. I are expecting a little
bit more romance
maybe unless drama.
But if you have any questions
about the language in this
lesson please visit the
website at englishpod.com.
Exactly Erica and I
are always there to
answer your questions and
well anything you guys need.
Anything? Anything?
Well thanks for listening
to this lesson and until next time.
Goodbye!